A Guide to the Libraries and Educational Technologies Records, 1939-2016, bulk 1988-2009: UA 0008
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Libraries and Educational Technologies Records,
1936-2016
(bulk 1988-2009)
Special Collections, James Madison University
Carrier Library
Libraries & Educational Technologies
Sharon Gasser
UA 0008
11.92 cubic feet; 35 boxes, 1 map folder
This collection of contains the administrative and financial records for JMU Libraries and Educational Technologies from 1939-2016. In addition to administrative records, this collection also contains historical items relating to the history of the library.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection. Collection is open for research. Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the James Madison University Special Collections Library to use this collection.
Acquisition Information
This collection was previously known as the Carrier Library Collection, LI-93-0406. In 2015 this collection was merged and reprocessed with the Carrier Library Vertical File as well as the LET Publications Vertical File along with multiple accessions from 2012, 2014, and 2015. Items from LI-93-0406 were placed in Series 6: Library History. Materials in the accessions included five linear feet from the Office of the Dean in 2012 and five linear feet from the office of Sharon Gasser, Associate Dean of Carrier Library in 2014. In 2015, three accessions were added. These include architectural renderings of Rose Library, ca. 2008, government documents, and files from the office of Reba Leiding, a former librarian at Carrier Library and Jody Hess, a former library staff member. The most recent accession in 2016 came from the filing cabinet in the Special Collections Reading Room and from the files of the departing Special Collections Librarian, Lynn Eaton.
Accruals
Receives regular additions of material.
Bio/Historical Note
James Madison University's first library was housed in Maury Hall and sat 40 students. In 1915, the library was moved to Harrison Hall, increasing its capacity to 98. Fifteen years later, a reading room was added to Harrison Hall, allowing it to seat 165 students and hold 20,000+ volumes. Despite these expansions, students called for a new building with more space and better lighting in October 1937. The following year, President Samuel Duke obtained funds from the Public Works Administration (PWA) and began construction on Madison Memorial Library. The library opened on September 22, 1939, seating 350 students and holding 80,000 volumes. Increased enrollment prompted additions in 1971, 1982, and 1994. Madison Memorial Library was renamed Carrier Library in 1984 after the fourth president of the university, Ronald Carrier. Today Carrier Library contains the humanities related collections.
In August 2008, the University built a second library on East Campus. East Campus Library (ECL) doubled the staffing and services of the library. ECL was renamed Rose Library in 2012 after the fifth president of the university, Linwood H. Rose. Rose Library holds the science related collections.
The University also has two subject specific libraries: the Music Library and the Educational Technology Media Center (ETMC). The Music Library is housed in the Music Building and provides scores, sound recordings, software titles, journals, and several special collections in support of the Music department. While not an official part of Libraries and Educational Technologies, the ETMC in Memorial Hall works with the College of Education to provide access, assistance, and maintenance to the library collection. The ETMC houses the juvenile collection, a small reference collection supported by the library materials budget, and the K-12 curriculum materials that support the College of Education.
In addition, Special Collections, located on the second floor of Carrier Library, was established in 1983 to document the history of JMU and the Central Shenandoah Valley. Today, Special Collections continues its mission of documenting the history of JMU and the Central Shenandoah Valley while also serving as Carrier Library's repository for rare and valuable materials and supporting JMU curriculum and community research through primary source materials.
The newest member of Library and Educational Technologies is Innovation Services, located in both Carrier and Rose Library. Innovation Services is focused on creative technologies, such as 3D Printing, video production, sound recording, and virtual reality, and making them available to the JMU community.
Scope and Content
The Libraries and Educational Technologies Records span from 1939 to 2016, with the bulk of the records from 1988 to 2009. The records detail the administrative functions of the library and document its position as an academic resource on the JMU campus. Records consist of financial records, committee reports, library policies, various subject files, and library history primarily from the Office of the Dean as well as the Associate Dean. The collection is arranged into six series.
Separated Material
Academic Program Review Self-Studies and External Team Reports were transferred to UA 0002: Academic Affairs: Academic Program Reviews, 1993 – Present. Statistical Summaries from the Office of Institutional Research were cataloged, and duplicates were discarded. All published monographs of Library Accession Records have been cataloged individually and placed in Special Collections' rare book collection. The accession records run continuously from September 1909 to February 1987, with the exception of 1974.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into six series and two subseries.
Series 1: Financial Records, 1975-2012
Subseries 1: Annual Reports, 1975-2012
Subseries 2: Budgets, 1982-2010 Series 2: Committees, 1987-2012 Series 3: Policies, 1989-2009 Series 4: Subject Files, 1975-2013 Series 5: Library Faculty and Staff, 1986-2003 Series 6: Library History, 1939-2016
Series 1: Financial Records is arranged chronologically; all other series are arranged alphabetically.
Index Terms
Subjects:
James Madison University. Libraries and Educational Technologies; James Madison University. Libraries; James Madison University -- History; Madison College -- History; Libraries and colleges; Academic Libraries -- Finance; Academic Libraries -- Administration; Academic Libraries -- Virginia -- Harrisonburg -- History
Genre and Form Terms:
CD-ROMS; DVDs; Printed Ephemera; Scrapbooks; Memorandums; Financial Records; Administrative records
- Financial Records, 1975-2012
  Scope and Content
  Arranged in two subseries: Annual Reports, 1975-2012 and Budgets, 1982-2010. Arranged chronologically within each series.
  Series 1: Financial Records, 1975-2012 is the largest series in the largest series within the collection. Most materials from this series are from 1980-2010, though some records are from as early as 1975. Annual Reports are an evaluative tool required by any program subject to Academic Program Review. These reports review the library's mission and goals, support the development of priorities, and contribution to strategic planning. The Annual Reports are from various departments within the library such as Periodicals, Serials, Technical Service Division, Educational Media Lab, and Collection Development, as well as a general summary report from JMU Libraries. The Budget subseries relates to collection management and acquisitions and contains many budgets for different areas of the library. Each budget is accompanied by an explanatory note.
  - Annual Reports, 1975-2012 (Box 1)
    - Annual Report FY1975-1976, 1984, 1975-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Annual Standing Order Report, 86/87-90/91, 1980-1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report FY1987-1988, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report FY1988-89, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report FY1989-90, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report FY1990-1991, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report FY1991-92, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report FY1992-93, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Annual Reports-Carrier Library, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report FY1993-94, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report FY1994-95, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report FY1995-96, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report FY1996-97, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report FY1997-98, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report FY1998-99, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report FY1999-2000, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report FY2000-01, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report 2000-2001, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report FY2001-2002, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 2002-03 Annual Reports, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report FY 2002-03, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report FY2003-04,, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report FY2004-05, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report FY2005-06, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report FY2006-07, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report FY2007-08, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report FY2008-09, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - SC/Preservation Annual Report, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Collections + TF Annual Report FY2009-2010, 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report 2010/11, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report 2011-12, 2011-2012 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Budgets, 1982-2010 (Box 4)
    - Budget- FY1982-83-FY1985-86, 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Budget- FY1986-87, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Budget- FY1987-88, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Budget- FY1988-89, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Budget-Biology (Historical), 1988-1992 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Budget- FY1988-89, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Budget- FY1989-90, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Budget- FY1990-91, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Financial Reports (Folder 1 of 2), 1990-2005 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Financial Reports (Folder 2 of 2), 1990-2005 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Budget- FY1991-92, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Budget- FY1991-92, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Budget- FY1992-93, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Budget- FY1992-93, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Budget- FY1993-94, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Budget- FY1994-95, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Budget- FY1994-95, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Operating Budget FY98/99, 1994-1999 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Budget- FY1995-96, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Budget- FY1996-97, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Budget- FY1997-98, 1996-2000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Budget FY1998-1999, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Budget FY1998-1999 Year End, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Budget FY1999-00 Fund Code Changes, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Budget 1999-00, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 1999-2000 Budget Prep, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - IT/ET Budgets 99/2000, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Budget FY1999-00 Year End, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Budget FY2000-01 Year End, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Budget- SACS Recommendations 2002-03, 1999, 2003-2008 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 1999-2000 End of the Year Budget, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - IT/ET Budget 2000-01, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Budget FY2000-01, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Budget FY2001-02, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Budget FY2002-03, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Budget FY2001-02 Year End, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Budget FY2002-03 Statistics, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Budget FY2002-03 Year End, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Budget FY2002-03 Vendor Performance, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Budget FY2003-04 Statistics, ca. 2003 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Budget FY2003-04, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Budget FY2003-04-Vendor Performance, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Budget FY2003-04-Year End, 2003-2005 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Budget FY2004-05, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Budget 2004-05-Financial Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Budget FY2004-05-Vendor Performance, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Budget-FY2004-05-Year End, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Budget FY2005-06-Financial Reports, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Budget FY2005-06-Statistics, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Budget FY2005-06-Vendor Performance, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Budget FY2005-06, 2005-2006, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Budget FY2005-06-Year End, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Budget FY2006-07, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Budget FY2006-07-Financial Papers, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Budget FY2006-07-Vendor Performance, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Budget FY2008-09-Allocations, 2006-2009 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Budget FY2007-08, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Budget FY2007-08-Allocations, 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Budget-FY2007-08-Financial Reports, 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Budget FY2007-08-Foundation, 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Budget FY2007-08-Vendor Performance, 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Budget FY2007-08 Year End, 2007-2009 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Budget FY2006-07-Year End, 2007-2009 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Budget FY2008-09, 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Budget FY2008/09-Financial Reports (Folder 1 of 2), 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Budget FY2008/09-Financial Reports (Folder 2 of 2), 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Budget FY2008-2009 Foundation, 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Budget FY2008/09-Vendor Performance, 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Budget- FY2008-09 Budget Reversions, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Budget FY2008/09- Year End, 2009-2010 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Committees, 1987-2012
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Series 2: Committees, 1987-2012 contains the records of committees within the library, committees associated with the library, and committees involving library staff. This series predominately contains records from the Academic Council and the Collection Development Committee. Records from the Academic Council include evaluations of current academic programs and suggestions for future improvement, minutes from meetings, and correspondences from President Carrier. Documents from the Collection Development Committee include meeting minutes, collection statistics, correspondences to academic departments, and plans of action. Also included in this series are various task force reports, evaluations of specific academic journals, and records from the commission of undergraduate studies, the graduate council, and the liberal studies committee. The majority of the records within this series pertain to the evaluation and advancement of the University's academic programs and the role of the library within those programs.
  - Academic Council 90-91, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Academic Council and President's Retreat 1993 (Folder 1 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council and President's Retreat 1993 (Folder 2 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Academic Council 95 (Folder 1 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Academic Council 95 (Folder 2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Academic Council 1996-97 (Folder 1 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council 1996-97 (Folder 2 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council 1998-1999 (Folder 1 of 3), 1997-2002 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Academic Council 1998-1999 (Folder 2 of 3), 1997-2002 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council 1998-1999 (Folder 3 of 3), 1997-2002 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Academic Council 1999-2000 (Folder 1 of 2), 1996-2002 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Academic Council 1999-2000 (Folder 2 of 2), 1996-2002 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council 2000-2001, 1998, 2000-2002 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council 2001-02, 1995, 1999-2002 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Biology Journal Review 2000, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Biology Journal Review 2003, 2000-2005 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Board of Visitors, 1990-2001 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Cluster Proposal FY2007-08, 2004, 2007-2009 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Collection Development Committee 2009-10, 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Collection Development Committee FY2000-01, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Collection Development Committee FY2001-02, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Collection Development Committee FY2002-03, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Collection Development Committee FY2003-04, 2003-2004 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Collection Development Committee FY2003-05, 2004-2005 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Collection Development Committee FY2005-06, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Collection Development Committee FY2006-07, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Collection Development Committee 2007, 2009, 2011-2012 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Collection Development Committee FY2007-08, 2007-2008 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Collection Development Committee FY2008-09, 2008-2009 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Collection Development Committee 2010-11, 2009-2011 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Collection Development Committee Strategic Planning Fall 2006, 2008, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Collection Development Committee Strategic Planning FY 2005-06, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Collection Development Policy, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Collection Development Policy Task Force, 2001, 2006, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Commission of Undergraduate Studies (Folder 1 of 2), 1990-1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Commission of Undergraduate Studies (Folder 2 of 2), 1990-1996 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Digital Access Management Committee, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Council (Folder 1 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Council (Folder 2 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Liberal Studies Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - The Madison Commission 2006-2012 (Folder 1 of 2), 2005-2006 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - The Madison Commission 2006-2012 (Folder 2 of 2), 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Pandemic Influenza Response Task Force, 2006-2007 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Serial Allocation Study AD-Hoc Comm. Allocation Formula Study, 1987, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Task Force, 1998-2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Task Force Recommendations (Folder 1 of 2), 1990-1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Task Force Recommendations (Folder 2 of 2), 1990-1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Teaching/Learning Center Task Force, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - University Curriculum Committee UCC, 1994-1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Policies, 1984-2009
  Series 3: Policies, 1984-2009 contains documents that outline various campus-wide and library-specific policies. The series runs continuously from 1984-2009, with the exception of 1986-1988 and 2003-2004. Materials within this series include documents that outline the process and prioritization of resource acquisition, and collection development, including faculty request and evaluation forms. Information on Federal collection development policies is also included. Also contained within this series are documents detailing various University policies. These include policies on harassment, academic program reviews, and policies regarding the enhancement of programs. Outlines of various University employment policies are housed in this series and include: the appointment and termination of faculty, recruitment of minority faculty, retirement procedures, and misconduct in research and scholarly work. Series 3: Policies, 1989-2009 also contains records of University self-studies and correspondences regarding the policies and regulations of the Commission on Colleges.
  - Academic Program Review, 1995, 1996, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Affiliation Agreement (JMU/GMU), 2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Database Selection Policy, 2001, 2005-2007, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Government Documents Collection Development, 1984, 1985, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Harassment, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Media Resources Collection Development Policy, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Policies, 1998, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Recruitment, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Reference Collection Development Policy, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - SACS, 1989-2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - SACS (Folder 1 of 2), 1999-2001, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - SACS (Folder 2 of 2), 1999-2001, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - SCHEV, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Special Collections Development Policy, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Task Force Curricula Programs Academic Policies, 1999, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Subject Files, 1973-2013
  Series 4: Subject Files, 1973-2013 contains a wide range of documents relating to the library's relationship with the academic departments of the University. The series is arranged alphabetically. Materials include collection development planning and evaluation, reports detailing the current state and future plans of various academic programs, and correspondences and documents to and from the Dean of Libraries & Educational Technologies. Many of the materials within this series aim to clarify and improve the library's role as an academic resource to the University. In addition, Box 34, Folder 4 contains media items that include: Photos of East Campus Library (now Rose Library) and Carrier Library, as well as photos from Ralph Alberico, former Dean of Libraries and Educational Technologies; CDs containing SACS Library Maps; the L&ET 2006 Self Study Report and Appendices; and one DVD, "The Library as Place."
  - Acquisitions/Serials Department 1991- (Folder 1 of 2), 1991-1996, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Acquisitions/Serials Department 1991- (Folder 2 of 2), 1991-1996, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Assessment-Carrier Library, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - CL Goals, 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Collections FY08, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Collections Development, 1990, 1995, 1999, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - College of Arts and Letters, 1986, 1982-1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - College of Business, 1988-1996 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - College of Education + Psych, 1986-1999 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - College of Science and Mathematics, 1994-1996, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth Classroom, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Communication Sciences + Disorders, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - County Courthouse Project, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - D.A.M. – Correspondence, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - D.A.M. – General, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Database, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Database Requests-FY2007-08, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Disabilities, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Displays/Exhibits, 1987-1988, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Endowments, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - External Team Reports, 1998 2007 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Appointments, 1996, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Handbook, 2000-2002 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Senate, 2001, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - General Education (Folder 1 of 2), 1996-1999 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - General Education (Folder 2 of 2), 1996-1999 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Gov Docs – Annual Reports (Folder 1 of 2), 1973-1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Gov Docs – Annual Reports (Folder 2 of 2), 1973-1995 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Gov Docs – Biennial Survey, 1973-1995 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Gov Docs – Depository Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Gov Docs – Depository Inspection, 1984-1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Gov Docs – DOCS Project, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Gov Docs – General (Folder 1 of 2), 1998-2009 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Gov Docs – General (Folder 2 of 2), 1998-2009 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Gov Docs – Instruction Manuals, 2002-2004 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Gov Docs – Justice Studies, 2011-2013 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Gov Docs – Leadership Studies, 2010-2011 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Gov Docs – Patents, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)